mixxbookmarks.info 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy | MixxBookmarks Blog | Free Social Bookmarking Information Tips and Resources |

PRIVACY POLICY FOR **MixxBookmarks** (includes MixxBookmarks.info website and MixxBookmarks Blog)

This privacy policy sets out how “ **MixxBookmarks** ” uses and protects any information that you give “ **MixxBookmarks** ” when you use this website.

“ **MixxBookmarks** ” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

“ **MixxBookmarks** ” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### **Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### **Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting **MixxBookmarks** , the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### **What We Collect**

We may collect the following information:

– Name

– Email Address

– Phone Numbers

– Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

– Information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

– Internal record keeping.

– We may use the information to improve our products and services.

– We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

– From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.

– We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### **Links To Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the material or content on those websites, or in regards to the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### **Your Personal Information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us via our “[ **Contact Us**](http://mixxbookmarks.info/blog/contact-us/ "Contact Us")” page..

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### **Google Adsense And The DoubleClick Dart Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. **MixxBookmarks** has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

### **Questions, Comments, or Report of Incidents**

If you have any questions, comments or reports regarding the privacy policy of **MixxBookmarks** then you may contact us via our[ **Contact Us**](http://mixxbookmarks.info/blog/contact-us/ "Contact Us") Form.

### **Revisions To This Privacy Policy Without Notice**

This Privacy Policy is dynamic. It will continually change. You may not assume that it remains the same and you agree to check the policy each time you visit the site for changes. Unless, in the sole opinion of the website, this policy changes so drastically as to suggest a posted notification on the site or via email, you will receive no notification of changes to this Privacy Policy nor, under any circumstances, does this site promise notification. Your continued use of this site always evidences your acceptance of the terms this Privacy Policy or any modifications.

_Last updated: Tuesday, 7th June 2011_
